Every inch of me is trembling
But not from the cold
Something is familiar
Like a dream I can reach
but not quite hold
I can sense you there
Like a friend I have always known
I am arriving
And it feels like I am home
I have always been a fortress
Cold secrets deep inside
You have secrets‚ too
But you don′t have to hide
Show yourself
I am dying to met you
It is your turn
Are you the one I have
been looking for
All of my life?
Show yourself
I am ready to learn
I have never felt so certain
All my life I have been torn
But I am here for a reason
Could it be the reason I was born?
I have always been so different
Normal rules did not apply
Is this the day?
Are you the way
I finally find out why?
Show yourself
I am no longer trembling
Here I am
I have come so far
You are the answer I have waited for
All of my life
Oh‚ show yourself
Let me see who you are
Come to me now
Open your door
Don′t make me wait
One moment more
Oh‚ come to me now
Open your door
Don′t make me wait
One moment more
Where the north wind mets the sea
There′s a river
Full of memory
Come‚ my darling‚ homeward bound
I am found
Show yourself
Step into your power
Grow yourself
Into something new
You are the one You have
been waiting for
All of my life
Oh‚ show yourself
You