I have been staring at the
edge of the water
Long as I can remember
Never really knowing why
I wish I could be the perfect daughter
But I come back to the water
No matter how hard I try
Every turn I take‚ every trail I track
Every path I make‚ every
road leads back
To the place I know where I cannot go
Where I long to be
See the line where the
sky mets the sea
It calls me
And no one knows
How far it goes
If the wind in my sail on
the sea stays behind me
One day I will know
If I go‚ there′s just no telling
how far I will go
I know everybody on this island
Seems so happy on this island
Everything is by design
(snorting)
I know everybody
On this island
(children laughing)
Has a role on this island
So maybe I can roll with mine
I can lead with pride‚
I can make us strong
I will be satisfied if I play along
But the voice inside sings
a different song
What is wrong with me?
See the light as it shines on the sea
It is blinding
But no one knows
How deep it goes
And it seems like It is
calling out to me
So come find me
And let me know
What′s beyond that line‚ will
I cross that line?
The line where the sky mets the sea
It calls me
And no one knows
How far it goes
If the wind in my sail on
the sea stays behind me
One day I will know
How far I will go
Whoa! (groans)
by RentAnAdviser.com