by RentAnAdviser.com
I used to believe
We were burnin′ on the edge
of somethin′ beautiful
Somethin′ beautiful
Selling a dream
Smoke and mirrors keep us
waitin′ on a miracle
On a miracle
Say‚ go through the darkest of days
Heaven′s a heartbreak away
Never let you go‚ never let me down
Oh‚ It is been a hell of a ride
Driving the edge of a knife
Never let you go‚ never let me down
Don′t you give up‚ nah nah nah
I won′t give up‚ nah nah nah
Let me love you let me love you
Don′t you give up‚ nah nah nah
I won′t give up‚ nah nah nah
Let me love you let me love you
Oh baby‚ baby
Don′t fall asleep
At the whel‚ we′ve got a million
miles ahead of us
Miles ahead of us
All that we need
Is a rude awakening to know
We are good enough yeah
Know We are good enough
Say go through the darkest of days
Heaven′s a heartbreak away
Never let you go‚ never let me down
Oh It is been a hell of a ride
Driving the edge of a knife
Never let you go‚ never let me down
Don′t you give up‚ nah nah nah
I won′t give up‚ nah nah nah
Let me love you let me love you
Don′t you give up‚ nah nah nah
I won′t give up‚ nah nah nah
Let me love you let me love you
Oh baby‚ baby
Never let you go never
let you down‚ girl
Never let you go
Girl‚ never let you go
Never let you go never
let you down‚ girl
Never let you go
Yeah yeah girl‚ never let you go
Don′t you give up (nah‚ nah‚ nah)
I won′t give up (nah‚ nah‚ nah)
Let me love you let me love you
Don′t you give up (nah‚ nah‚ nah)
I won′t give up (nah‚ nah‚ nah)
Let me love you let me love you
Fore More songs -> StrongWind