by RentAnAdviser.com
I found a love for me
Darling just dive right in
And follow my lead
Well I found a girl beautiful
and sweet
I never knew you were the
someone waiting for me
′Cause we were just kids
when we fell in love
Not knowing what it was
I will not give you up this time
But darling‚ just kiss me slow‚
your heart is all I own
And in your eyes You are holding mine
Baby‚ I am dancing in the dark
with you between my arms
Barefoot on the grass‚ listening
to our favorite song
When you said you looked a mess‚ I
whispered underneath my breath
But you heard it‚ darling‚
you look perfect tonight
Well I found a woman‚ stronger
than anyone I know
She shares my dreams‚ I hope that
someday I will share her home
I found a love‚ to carry more
than just my secrets
To carry love‚ to carry
children of our own
We are still kids‚ but
We are so in love
Fighting against all odds
I know we′ll be alright this time
Darling‚ just hold my hand
Be my girl‚ I will be your man
I see my future in your eyes
Baby‚ I am dancing in the dark‚
with you between my arms
Barefoot on the grass‚ listening
to our favorite song
When I saw you in that dress‚
looking so beautiful
I don′t deserve this‚ darling‚
you look perfect tonight
Baby‚ I am dancing in the dark‚
with you between my arms
Barefoot on the grass‚ listening
to our favorite song
I have faith in what I see
Now I know I have met
an angel in person
And she looks perfect
I don′t deserve this
You look perfect tonight
For more songs -> Strongwind